questions:
  - question: Base attack of the green hero **Abaddon**?
    answer: 4
  - question: Base health of the green hero **Abaddon**?
    answer: 9
  - question: Base attack of the red hero **Axe**?
    answer: 7
  - question: Base health of the red hero **Axe**?
    answer: 11
  - question: Base attack of the red hero **Tidehunter**?
    answer: 2
  - question: Base health of the red hero **Tidehunter**?
    answer: 18
  - question: Base attack of the red hero **Centaur Warrunner**?
    answer: 4
  - question: Base health of the red hero **Centaur Warrunner**?
    answer: 14
  - question: Base attack of the black hero **Bloodseeker**?
    answer: 7
  - question: Base health of the black hero **Bloodseeker**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base attack of the red hero **Bristleback**?
    answer: 8
  - question: Base health of the red hero **Bristleback**?
    answer: 12
  - question: Base attack of the green hero **Chen**?
    answer: 4
  - question: Base health of the green hero **Chen**?
    answer: 9
  - question: Base attack of the blue hero **Crystal Maiden**?
    answer: 2
  - question: Base health of the blue hero **Crystal Maiden**?
    answer: 5
  - question: Base attack of the blue hero **Earthshaker**?
    answer: 2
  - question: Base health of the blue hero **Earthshaker**?
    answer: 7
  - question: Base attack of the black hero **Bounty Hunter**?
    answer: 7
  - question: Base health of the black hero **Bounty Hunter**?
    answer: 7
  - question: Base attack of the red hero **Timbersaw**?
    answer: 4
  - question: Base health of the red hero **Timbersaw**?
    answer: 11
  - question: Base attack of the green hero **Enchantress**?
    answer: 4
  - question: Base health of the green hero **Enchantress**?
    answer: 8
  - question: Base attack of the green hero **Fahrvan**?
    answer: 4
  - question: Base health of the green hero **Fahrvan**?
    answer: 11
  - question: Base attack of the green hero **Treant Protector**?
    answer: 4
  - question: Base health of the green hero **Treant Protector**?
    answer: 10
  - question: Base attack of the blue hero **J'Muy**?
    answer: 3
  - question: Base health of the blue hero **J'Muy**?
    answer: 8
  - question: Base attack of the blue hero **Kanna**?
    answer: 2
  - question: Base health of the blue hero **Kanna**?
    answer: 12
  - question: Base attack of the red hero **Beastmaster**?
    answer: 5
  - question: Base health of the red hero **Beastmaster**?
    answer: 12
  - question: Base attack of the red hero **Keefe**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base health of the red hero **Keefe**?
    answer: 11
  - question: Base attack of the red hero **Legion Commander**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base health of the red hero **Legion Commander**?
    answer: 8
  - question: Base attack of the black hero **Lich**?
    answer: 5
  - question: Base health of the black hero **Lich**?
    answer: 9
  - question: Base attack of the black hero **Lion**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base health of the black hero **Lion**?
    answer: 5
  - question: Base attack of the green hero **Magnus**?
    answer: 4
  - question: Base health of the green hero **Magnus**?
    answer: 9
  - question: Base attack of the red hero **Mazzie**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base health of the red hero **Mazzie**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base attack of the green hero **Omniknight**?
    answer: 5
  - question: Base health of the green hero **Omniknight**?
    answer: 12
  - question: Base attack of the black hero **Phantom Assassin**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base health of the black hero **Phantom Assassin**?
    answer: 8
  - question: Base attack of the blue hero **Venomancer**?
    answer: 2
  - question: Base health of the blue hero **Venomancer**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base attack of the blue hero **Outworld Devourer**?
    answer: 4
  - question: Base health of the blue hero **Outworld Devourer**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base attack of the blue hero **Prellex**?
    answer: 3
  - question: Base health of the blue hero **Prellex**?
    answer: 5
  - question: Base attack of the black hero **Riley**?
    answer: 7
  - question: Base health of the black hero **Riley**?
    answer: 5
  - question: Base attack of the green hero **Rix**?
    answer: 3
  - question: Base health of the green hero **Rix**?
    answer: 7
  - question: Base attack of the blue hero **Skywrath Mage**?
    answer: 3
  - question: Base health of the blue hero **Skywrath Mage**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base attack of the black hero **Sniper**?
    answer: 5
  - question: Base health of the black hero **Sniper**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base attack of the black hero **Sorla Khan**?
    answer: 8
  - question: Base health of the black hero **Sorla Khan**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base attack of the red hero **Sven**?
    answer: 5
  - question: Base health of the red hero **Sven**?
    answer: 11
  - question: Base attack of the black hero **Storm Spirit**?
    answer: 4
  - question: Base health of the black hero **Storm Spirit**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base attack of the red hero **Ursa**?
    answer: 7
  - question: Base health of the red hero **Ursa**?
    answer: 10
  - question: Base attack of the black hero **Winter Wyvern**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base health of the black hero **Winter Wyvern**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base attack of the blue hero **Zeus**?
    answer: 3
  - question: Base health of the blue hero **Zeus**?
    answer: 7
  - question: Base attack of the red hero **Pugna**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base health of the red hero **Pugna**?
    answer: 9
  - question: Base attack of the black hero **Necrophos**?
    answer: 5
  - question: Base health of the black hero **Necrophos**?
    answer: 6
  - question: Base attack of the blue hero **Meepo**?
    answer: 4
  - question: Base health of the blue hero **Meepo**?
    answer: 5
  - question: Base attack of the green hero **Lycan**?
    answer: 4
  - question: Base health of the green hero **Lycan**?
    answer: 10
  - question: Base attack of the blue hero **Ogre Magi**?
    answer: 3
  - question: Base health of the blue hero **Ogre Magi**?
    answer: 7
  - question: Base attack of the blue hero **Luna**?
    answer: 3
  - question: Base health of the blue hero **Luna**?
    answer: 8
  - question: Base attack of **Savage Wolf**?
    answer: 3
  - question: Base health of **Savage Wolf**?
    answer: 3
  - question: Base health of **Thunderhide Pack**?
    answer: 14
  - question: Base attack of **Thunderhide Pack**?
    answer: 14
  - question: "How much mana does the Green spell **Act of Defiance** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Green spell **Allseeing One's Favor** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Annihilation** cost?"
    answer: 6
  - question: "How much mana does the Green spell **Aphotic Shield** cost?"
    answer: 2
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Assassinate** cost?"
    answer: 7
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Diabolic Revelation** cost?"
    answer: 1
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Battlefield Control** cost?"
    answer: 1
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Primal Roar** cost?"
    answer: 7
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Berserker's Call** cost?"
    answer: 6
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Double Edge** cost?"
    answer: 1
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Better Late Than Never** cost?"
    answer: 3
  - question: "How much mana does the Green spell **Corrosive Mist** cost?"
    answer: 5
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **And One For Me** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Clear the Deck** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Combat Training** cost?"
    answer: 3
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Blood Rage** cost?"
    answer: 5
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Coup de Grace** cost?"
    answer: 6
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Cunning Plan** cost?"
    answer: 2
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Defensive Stance** cost?"
    answer: 2
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Dimensional Portal** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Divided We Stand** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Green spell **Iron Branch Protection** cost?"
    answer: 2
  - question: "How much mana does the Green spell **Divine Purpose** cost?"
    answer: 7
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Slay** cost?"
    answer: 3
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Hip Fire** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Arcane Censure** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Gank** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Duel** cost?"
    answer: 2
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Echo Slam** cost?"
    answer: 7
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Eclipse** cost?"
    answer: 6
  - question: "How much mana does the Green spell **Empower** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Enough Magic!** cost?"
    answer: 5
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Enrage** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Fighting Instinct** cost?"
    answer: 5
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Foresight** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Friendly Fire** cost?"
    answer: 6
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Frostbite** cost?"
    answer: 3
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **God's Strength** cost?"
    answer: 6
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Dirty Deeds** cost?"
    answer: 3
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Remote Detonation** cost?"
    answer: 6
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Pick a Fight** cost?"
    answer: 2
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Sucker Punch** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Crack the Whip** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Fight Through The Pain** cost?"
    answer: 1
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Heroic Resolve** cost?"
    answer: 2
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Rising Anger** cost?"
    answer: 2
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Grazing Shot** cost?"
    answer: 1
  - question: "How much mana does the Green spell **Hand of God** cost?"
    answer: 7
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Kraken Shell** cost?"
    answer: 1
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Heartstopper Aura** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Bolt of Damocles** cost?"
    answer: 10
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Buying Time** cost?"
    answer: 3
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Collateral Damage** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Chain Frost** cost?"
    answer: 7
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Mana Drain** cost?"
    answer: 2
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Mystic Flare** cost?"
    answer: 6
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **New Orders** cost?"
    answer: 1
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **No Accident** cost?"
    answer: 3
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Payday** cost?"
    answer: 3
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Pick Off** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Spring the Trap** cost?"
    answer: 7
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Poised to Strike** cost?"
    answer: 1
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Sow Venom** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Prey on the Weak** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Green spell **Defensive Bloom** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Murder Plot** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Relentless Pursuit** cost?"
    answer: 1
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Strafing Run** cost?"
    answer: 1
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Take Aim** cost?"
    answer: 1
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Thunder God's Wrath** cost?"
    answer: 7
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Time of Triumph** cost?"
    answer: 8
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Tower Barrage** cost?"
    answer: 3
  - question: "How much mana does the Green spell **Truth to Power** cost?"
    answer: 5
  - question: "How much mana does the Blue spell **Ventriloquy** cost?"
    answer: 1
  - question: "How much mana does the Red spell **Viscous Nasal Goo** cost?"
    answer: 4
  - question: "How much mana does the Black spell **Winter's Curse** cost?"
    answer: 6
  - question: What is the name of **Axe**'s signature spell?
    answer: Berserker's Call
  - question: What is the name of **Abaddon**'s signature spell?
    answer: Aphotic Shield
  - question: What is the name of **Tidehunter**'s signature spell?
    answer: Kraken Shell
  - question: What is the name of **Centaur Warrunner**'s signature spell?
    answer: Double Edge
  - question: What is the name of **Bristleback**'s signature spell?
    answer: Viscous Nasal Goo
  - question: What is the name of **Chen**'s signature spell?
    answer: Hand of God
  - question: What is the name of **Crystal Maiden**'s signature spell?
    answer: Frostbite
  - question: What is the name of **Earthshaker**'s signature spell?
    answer: Echo Slam
  - question: What is the name of **Fahrvan**'s signature spell?
    answer: Prowler Vanguard
  - question: What is the name of **J'Muy**'s signature spell?
    answer: Battlefield Control
  - question: What is the name of **Kanna**'s signature spell?
    answer: Prey on the Weak
  - question: What is the name of **Beastmaster**'s signature spell?
    answer: Primal Roar
  - question: What is the name of **Keefe**'s signature spell?
    answer: Fighting Instinct
  - question: What is the name of **Legion Commander**'s signature spell?
    answer: Duel
  - question: What is the name of **Lich**'s signature spell?
    answer: Chain Frost
  - question: What is the name of **Lion**'s signature spell?
    answer: Mana Drain
  - question: What is the name of **Luna**'s signature spell?
    answer: Eclipse
  - question: What is the name of **Lycan**'s signature spell?
    answer: Savage Wolf
  - question: What is the name of **Magnus**'s signature spell?
    answer: Empower
  - question: What is the name of **Mazzie**'s signature spell?
    answer: Steel Reinforcements
  - question: What is the name of **Meepo**'s signature spell?
    answer: Divided We Stand
  - question: What is the name of **Necrophos**'s signature spell?
    answer: Heartstopper Aura
  - question: What is the name of **Omniknight**'s signature spell?
    answer: Allseeing One's Favor
  - question: What is the name of **Phantom Assasin**'s signature spell?
    answer: Coup de Grace
  - question: What is the name of **Venomancer**'s signature spell?
    answer: Sow Venom
  - question: What is the name of **Prellex**'s signature spell?
    answer: Barracks
  - question: What is the name of **Pugna**'s signature spell?
    answer: Nether Ward
  - question: What is the name of **Riley**'s signature spell?
    answer: No Accident
  - question: What is the name of **Rix**'s signature spell?
    answer: Truth to Power
  - question: What is the name of **Skywrath Mage**'s signature spell?
    answer: Mystic Flare
  - question: What is the name of **Sniper**'s signature spell?
    answer: Assassinate
  - question: What is the name of **Sorla Khan**'s signature spell?
    answer: Assault Ladders
  - question: What is the name of **Ursa**'s signature spell?
    answer: Enrage
  - question: What is the name of **Winter Wyvern**'s signature spell?
    answer: Winter's Curse
  - question: What is the name of **Zeus**'s signature spell?
    answer: Thunder God's Wrath
  - question: What color is the hero **Phantom Assasin** from?
    answer: Black
  - question: How much gold does **Blink Dagger** cost?
    answer: 7
  - question: How much gold does **Healing Salve** cost?
    answer: 3
  - question: How much gold does **Phase Boots** cost?
    answer: 6
  - question: How much gold does **Potion of Knowledge** cost?
    answer: 5
  - question: How much gold does **Shiva's Guard** cost?
    answer: 16
  - question: How much gold does **Short Sword** cost?
    answer: 3
  - question: How much gold does **Stonehall Cloak** cost?
    answer: 5
  - question: How much gold does **Town Portal Scroll** cost?
    answer: 3
  - question: How much gold does **Keenfolk Musket** cost?
    answer: 7
  - question: How much gold does **Horn of the Alpha** cost?
    answer: 25
  - question: How much gold does **Hero's Cape** cost?
    answer: 15
  - question: How much gold does **Apotheosis Blade** cost?
    answer: 25
  - question: How much gold does **Claymore** cost?
    answer: 15
  - question: "Fill the description for **Hero's Cape**: `Equipped hero has +_ Health.`"
    answer: 16
  - question: "Fill the description for **Traveler's Cloak**: `Equipped hero has +_ Health.`"
    answer: 4
  - question: "Fill the description for **Leather Armor**: `Equipped hero has +_ Armor.`"
    answer: 1
  - question: "Fill the description for **Foresight**: `Draw _ cards.`"
    answer: 2
  - question: "Fill the description for **Poaching Knife**: `Equipped hero has +_ Attack. Get 5 gold after an enemy hero dies. Get 1 gold after an enemy creep dies.`"
    answer: 2
  - question: "Fill the description for **Poaching Knife**: `Equipped hero has +2 Attack. Get _ gold after an enemy hero dies. Get 1 gold after an enemy creep dies.`"
    answer: 5
  - question: "Fill the description for **Poaching Knife**: `Equipped hero has +2 Attack. Get 5 gold after an enemy hero dies. Get _ gold after an enemy creep dies.`"
    answer: 1
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Modify allied creeps with +2 Attack and +1 Armor.`"
    answer: Act of Defiance
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Modify a green hero with 'Allies have +2 Regeneration'`"
    answer: Allseeing One's Favor
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Condemn all units.`"
    answer: Annihilation
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Purge enemy effects from a unit. Give that unit +2 Armor and +2 Retaliate this round.`"
    answer: Aphotic Shield
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Deal 10 piercing damage to a unit in any lane.`"
    answer: Assassinate
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Draw 2 cards. Deal 2 damage to allies in all lanes.`"
    answer: Diabolic Revelation
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Choose a unit. Choose a combat target for it.`"
    answer: Battlefield Control
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Stun a unit blocking an allied red hero this round. Move that unit's allied neighbors to random other lanes.`"
    answer: Primal Roar
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Choose an allied red hero. It battles its enemy neighbors.`"
    answer: Berserker's Call
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Give a red hero +8 Attack and -8 Armor this round.`"
    answer: Double Edge
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Summon a Melee Creep into any lane.`"
    answer: Better Late Than Never
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Condemn all equipped items.`"
    answer: Corrosive Mist
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Choose a hero. Put a base copy of a random item equipped by that hero into your hand.`"
    answer: And One For Me
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Give allied heroes +4 Cleave this round.`"
    answer: Clear the Deck
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Modify a hero with +2 Attack.`"
    answer: Combat Training
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Silence a unit this round. Give that unit +4 Attack this round.`"
    answer: Blood Rage
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Condemn  hero. Discard a random card.`"
    answer: Coup de Grace
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Swap a unit with one of its allied neighbors. Draw a card.`"
    answer: Cunning Plan
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Unknown`"
    answer: Defensive Stance
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Summon 3 Melee Creeps`"
    answer: Dimensional Portal
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Summon a Meepo`"
    answer: Divided We Stand
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Give a unit in any lane +3 Armor until end of its next combat phase.`"
    answer: Iron Branch Protection
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Modify a unit with Damage Immunity.`"
    answer: Divine Purpose
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Condemn a creep.`"
    answer: Slay
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Deal 4 Damage to a unit. Get Initiative.`"
    answer: Hip Fire
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Modify the enemy tower with -1 Mana.`"
    answer: Arcane Censure
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Choose an allied black hero. Choose another unit in any lane. They battle each other.`"
    answer: Gank
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Choose an allied red hero and another unit. They battle each other.`"
    answer: Duel
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Deal damage to each enemy equal to the number of enemies.`"
    answer: Echo Slam
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Repeat 1 time for each charge: Deal 3 piercing damage to a random enemy.`"
    answer: Eclipse
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Modify a unit with +3 Attack and +3 Cleave.`"
    answer: Empower
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Proceed to the combat phase`"
    answer: Enough Magic!
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Give a red hero +4 Attack and +4 Armor this round.`"
    answer: Enrage
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Modify a red hero with +1 Attack and +1 Armor.`"
    answer: Fighting Instinct
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Draw 2 cards.`"
    answer: Foresight
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Choose two enemies. They battle each other.`"
    answer: Friendly Fire
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Deal 2 damage to a unit and disarm it this round`"
    answer: Frostbite
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Unknown`"
    answer: God's Strength
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Deal 2 damage to the enemy tower for each of its improvements.`"
    answer: Dirty Deeds
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Deal 5 damage to each enemy without a blocker.`"
    answer: Remote Detonation
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Choose an allied hero. It taunts. Choose a combat target for it.`"
    answer: Pick a Fight
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Stun a unit blocking an allied red hero this round. Deal 2 damage to that unit.'`"
    answer: Sucker Punch
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Modify a black hero with 'After you play a black card, give this hero and its allied neighbors +2 Attack this round.'`"
    answer: Crack the Whip
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Give a red hero +2 Armor this round. Get Initiative`"
    answer: Fight Through The Pain
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Modify a red hero with 'After you play a non-item card costing 2 or less, modify this hero with +2 Health.'`"
    answer: Heroic Resolve
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Modify a red hero with 'After you play a non-item card costing 2 or less, modify this hero with +1 Attack.'`"
    answer: Rising Anger
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Deal 2 damage to a unit in any lane.`"
    answer: Grazing Shot
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Fully heal each ally. Give allies Damage Immunity this round.`"
    answer: Hand of God
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Modify a red hero with +1 Armor. Get initiative.`"
    answer: Kraken Shell
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Modify a black hero with 'Deal 2 Piercing damage to this hero's enemy neighbors before the action phase'`"
    answer: Heartstopper Aura
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Deal 20 damage to the enemy tower.`"
    answer: Bolt of Damocles
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Give two random cards in opponent's hand +2 Lock.`"
    answer: Buying Time
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Modify a black hero with +3 Siege.'`"
    answer: Collateral Damage
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Deal 3 damage to a unit. Repeat 7 times: Deal 3 damage to a random unit to the left or right. Get initiative.`"
    answer: Chain Frost
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Give the enemy tower -2 Mana this round and give your tower +2 Mana this round.`"
    answer: Mana Drain
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Deal 12 damage evenly divided among a unit and its allied negihbors.`"
    answer: Mystic Flare
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Choose an ally. Choose a combat target for it.`"
    answer: New Orders
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Deal 3 damage to a unit.`"
    answer: No Accident
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Double your gold.`"
    answer: Payday
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Deal 4 damage to a unit in any lane.`"
    answer: Pick Off
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Summon two Centaur Hunters into any lane.`"
    answer: Spring the Trap
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Give a red hero +4 Attack this round.`"
    answer: Poised to Strike
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Summon two Plague Wards.`"
    answer: Sow Venom
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Summon a Hound of War for every damaged unit.`"
    answer: Prey on the Weak
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Summon two Roseleaf Walls`"
    answer: Defensive Bloom
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Give a black hero +8 Attack this round. Choose a combat target for it.`"
    answer: Murder Plot
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Choose a unit in another lane. Move a random allied black hero from this lane to that lane. Deal 2 damage to the chosen unit.`"
    answer: Relentless Pursuit
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Deal 2 damage to each enemy creep.`"
    answer: Strafing Run
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Give a red hero +4 Attack this round.`"
    answer: Take Aim
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Deal 4 piercing damage to each enemy hero in all lanes.`"
    answer: Thunder God's Wrath
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Modify allied heroes with +4 Attack, +4 Armor, +4 Cleave, +4 Retaliate, and +4 Siege.`"
    answer: Time of Triumph
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Deal 2 damage to each enemy.`"
    answer: Tower Barrage
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Silence a unit this round.`"
    answer: Truth to Power
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Choose a unit. It taunts.`"
    answer: Ventriloquy
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Modify a unit with -2 Armor.`"
    answer: Viscous Nasal Goo
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Disarm a unit until end of round. That units allied neighbors battle it.`"
    answer: Winter's Curse
  - question: "Name the spell with this text: `Purge enemy effects from a unit. Give that unit +2 Armor and +2 Retaliate this round.`"
    answer: Aphotic Shield
  - question: "Which color does the card with this text belong to: `Allied Melee Creeps have +2 Regeneration.`?"
    answer: Green
  - question: "Which color does the card with this text belong to: `Summon a Melee Creep into this lane each deployment phase.`?"
    answer: Blue
